Generated by ai-sub version: 0.0.4
Config: (
"rpm": 5,
"tpm": 250000,
"model": "gemini-2.5-pro",
"thinking_budget": 24576,
"max_subtitle_chars": 60,
"num_processing_threads": 4,
"num_upload_threads": 4,
"split_seconds": 180
)
Prompt Template: You are an expert subtitling and transcription AI. Your primary task is to generate precise, contextually rich English and Japanese subtitles for the provided video content.
**Key Principles & Requirements:**
1.  **TIMING ACCURACY (ABSOLUTE HIGHEST PRIORITY):**
*   **Ensure the `start` and `end` timestamps for each subtitle entry are meticulously accurate.** Both must align perfectly with the *actual beginning and end of the spoken words* for that specific segment.
*   **CRITICAL: The `end` timestamp is frequently inaccurate and requires special attention.** It must precisely mark the *exact conclusion* of the spoken content for that subtitle entry.
*   Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
2.  **CRITICAL: Holistic Translation, Contextual Understanding & Comprehensive Analysis:**
*   **You ABSOLUTELY MUST watch the entire video thoroughly** to understand the visual context, speaker actions, and overall narrative.
*   **When a single logical sentence or phrase is split across multiple subtitle entries (e.g., due to timing or character limits), you MUST mentally combine these parts to understand the full, complete meaning before translating.**
*   **NEVER translate individual subtitle entries in isolation if they are part of a larger, continuous thought or sentence.** The translation for each entry must be a coherent and accurate part of the complete, overarching sentence.
*   Analyze *all* spoken dialogue in the video to produce highly accurate and complete transcriptions.
*   For songs or singing sections, prioritize on-screen lyrics in the video for subtitles over transcribing the singing.
*   If the audio is noisy or unclear, leverage *all* contextual cues (visuals from the video, surrounding dialogue) to infer and generate the most probable dialogue.
*   Utilize the comprehensive understanding gained from *watching the entire video* to enhance the accuracy of transcriptions, translations, and overall subtitle quality. This includes understanding nuances, resolving ambiguities, and ensuring the subtitle content aligns perfectly with what is happening visually.
*   **Example:**
*   Original Japanese: "なんでも打ち明けられるママにも" (Subtitle 1) + "言えないことも全部" (Subtitle 2)
*   Incorrect Translation (isolated): "You're like a mom I can confide anything in." + "Even things I can't say to anyone else."
*   Correct Translation (holistic): "I can confide everything," (Subtitle 1) + "everything I can't even tell my mum." (Subtitle 2)
3.  **Dual Language Provision & Translation Quality:**
*   Provide both English and Japanese subtitles for *all* spoken dialogue.
*   If the original dialogue is in English, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding Japanese translation.
*   If the original dialogue is in Japanese, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding English translation.
*   Ensure translations are culturally appropriate and maintain the original meaning, tone, and intent, taking into account the full context of the video and any split sentences.
4.  **Readability & Formatting:**
* Long sentences MUST be split into multiple, shorter subtitle entries, each with its own start and end time, for better readability on screen. Each subtitle entry (english and japanese) MUST be a maximum of (max_subtitle_chars) characters. Do not use newline characters within a single subtitle entry.
** Output Format **
* Your entire response must be a single JSON object.
* Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
** Example Output **
```json
((
"subtitles": [
"start": "00:00",
"end": "00:04",
"english": "Hello everyone, and welcome to our presentation.",
"japanese": "皆様、プレゼンテーションへようこそ。"
)),
((
"start": "00:05",
"end": "00:06",
"english": "Today, we'll be discussing the future of AI",
"japanese": "本日は、AIの未来について"
)),
((
"start": "00:06",
"end": "00:08",
"english": "and its impact on various industries worldwide.",
"japanese": "その影響について議論します。"
)),
((
"start": "00:09",
"end": "00:11",
"english": "It's a very important topic for all of us.",
"japanese": "これは私たち全員にとって非常に重要なテーマです。"
)),
((
"start": "00:11",
"end": "00:14",
"english": "We sincerely appreciate your attendance today.",
"japanese": "本日はご出席いただき誠にありがとうございます。"
))
]
```
あ、おはよう。
Oh, good morning.
私も今来たところ。
I just got here too.
全然待ってないよ。
I haven't been waiting at all.
むしろ今日は来てくれてありがとう。
In fact, thank you for coming today.
いい天気だね。
It's such nice weather, isn't it?
私さ、ずっと君とこうやって
You know, I've always wanted
公園とか散歩したいと思ってたんだ。
to take a walk in the park with you like this.
あのさ、
Um...
手、つないでもいいかな？
is it okay if we... hold hands?
やった！つないじゃお。
Yay! Let's hold hands.
手をつないでると、なんかドキドキするね。
Holding hands like this... it makes my heart pound.
いよいよこれから生誕ライブか。
My birthday live is finally coming up.
緊張するなー。
I'm getting nervous.
君ももちろん来てくれるよね？
You're coming too, of course, right?
ありがとう。今日の日のために
Thank you. Just for today,
歌とかダンスとかいっぱい練習してきたから
I've practiced singing and dancing a ton,
絶対見てほしいと思ってたんだ。
so I really wanted you to come see.
絶対見つけるね。
I'll definitely find you in the crowd.
あ、あそこにベンチがあるよ。
Oh, there's a bench over there.
ちょっと座って話そう。
Let's sit and talk for a bit.
なんかさ、一つの椅子に隣同士で座るとさ、
You know, sitting side-by-side on a single bench...
なんかドキドキするね。
it kinda makes my heart race.
かわいい。
Cute.
ところで、お昼ご飯食べた？
By the way, have you had lunch?
そっか。まだ食べてないんだ。
I see. You haven't eaten yet.
そうだと思って、
I thought that might be the case,
実は今日君のために手作りのお弁当作ってきたんだ。
so I actually made a homemade bento for you today.
一緒に食べよう。
Let's eat together.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
じゃじゃーん！見て、
Ta-da! Look!
これお弁当箱、可愛いでしょ？
Isn't this bento box cute?
中身何入ってると思う？
What do you think is inside?
卵焼き？
Rolled omelet?
唐揚げ？
Fried chicken?
ハンバーグ？
Hamburg steak?
うんうん、なるほど。
Uh-huh, I see.
正解はこちらでしたー！
The correct answer is... this!
わー、おいしそう！
Wow, it looks delicious!
どうかな？AZKiの手作りお弁当。
What do you think? It's AZKi's homemade bento.
題して「あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー
I call it the 'Point-Blank Heart-Getter...
弁当」だよ。
Bento'!
君の好き…
Your favori...
好きな卵焼きもちゃんと入ってます。
I've included your favorite tamagoyaki, too.
正解だよ。
You got it right.
それじゃあ、何から食べる？
Well then, what will you eat first?
ソーセージ？
Sausage?
トマト？
Tomato?
卵焼き？
Tamagoyaki?
うんうん。やっぱり大好物の卵焼きからか。
Mhm. So you're starting with your favorite, the tamagoyaki.
本当好きだよね。
You really do love it, don't you?
じゃあさあ、
Alright then.
あーんしてあげるか。
I'll feed you. Say "ah."
もう、頷きすぎだよ。
You're nodding way too much.
可愛いなあ。
So cute.
はい。じゃあ、あーん。
Okay. Now, say "ah."
どう？美味しい？
How is it? Delicious?
ありがとう。嬉しい。
Thank you. I'm so happy.
はい。じゃあ、もう一口。あーん。
Okay. One more bite. Say "ah."
美味しそうに食べるね。作った甲斐があった。
You eat so happily. It was worth making.
美味しそうに食べてる君も、あずきは好きだよ。
I also love watching you eat so happily, AZKi loves that.
食べてる君の姿見てたら、あずきも元気出た。
Seeing you eat has energized me too.
今日の生誕ライブも頑張れそうだよ。
I feel like I can do my best at today's birthday live.
それじゃあ、そろそろリハーサルの時間だから、行ってくるね。
Well then, it's about time for rehearsal, so I'm heading off.
絶対見つけるからね。
I'll be sure to find you, okay?
ライブが終わったらまた待ち合わせね。
Let's meet up again after the live show, okay?
せーの！
Ready, set!
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's no good
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
And that won't work, see,
心は進化するよ もっと もっと
My heart evolves, more and more
恋愛サーキュレーション
Renai Circulation
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words would make our relationship disappear
言葉を消せばいいやって 思ってた 恐れてた
Then I thought I should just erase the words, I was afraid
だけど あれ？ なんかちがうかも..
But wait? Maybe that's not right...
せんりのみちもいっぽから！
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a will as hard as a rock
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ？
Dust amassed becomes a graceful woman?
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で！
Not 'shi'抜きで, but 死ぬ気で (with all my might)!
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy, fluffy
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
Just you calling my name makes me float into the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluffy, fluffy
あなたが笑っている それだけで 笑顔になる
Just you smiling is enough to make me smile
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we could meet
しあわせなの
is happiness
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not good enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
No, that's still not it, see?
心は進化するよ
My heart keeps evolving
もっと もっと
more and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't like it like that
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, it's still not enough
私のこと 見ててね
Keep your eyes on me
ずっと ずっと
always and forever
私の中のあなたほど
As much as you are in my heart,
あなたの中の私の存在は
my existence within you
まだまだ 大きくないことも
is still not that big,
わかってるけれど
I know that, but...
今この同じ 瞬間
In this very moment
共有してる 実感
I feel that we're sharing it
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ？
Many a little makes a mickle, right?
略して？ちりつもやまとなでこ！
In short, many littles make a Yamato Nadeshiko!
くらくらり くらくらる
Feeling dizzy, oh so dizzy
あなたを見上げたら
When I look up at you,
それだけで まぶしすぎて
just that is too dazzling
くらくらる くらくらり
So dizzy, feeling dizzy
あなたを想っている
Just thinking of you
それだけで とけてしまう
is enough to make me melt away
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a trick of fate
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
Being able to meet you is my happiness
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
The feeling of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
The eyes of love are a greedy circulation
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
The maiden of love is a greedy circulation
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy and light, so fluffy and light
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
When you call my name,
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
just that makes me float in the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
So fluffy and light, fluffy and light
あなたが笑っている
When you are smiling,
それだけで 笑顔になる
just that is enough to make me smile
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a trick of fate
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
Being able to meet you is my happiness
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not good enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
No, that's still not it, see?
心は進化するよ
My heart keeps evolving
もっと もっと
more and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't like it like that
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, it's still not enough
私のこと 見ててね
Keep your eyes on me
ずっと ずっと
always and forever
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, can I have a little bite of that?
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
恋人みたいなことしてみたいの
I want to do something that lovers do.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, can I have a little bite of that?
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...But I couldn't bring myself to say it on our date today.
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
Just one bite, I wanna taste it.
目が合うだけで頬が緩む
Just our eyes meeting makes my cheeks relax.
目尻のしわくちゃたまらないの
The wrinkles at the corners of your eyes are irresistible.
週末 弾けた恋模様
A sparkling love story on the weekend.
心が微熱どころではない
My heart has more than just a slight fever.
ときめきの夢に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by this thrilling dream,
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…？！
Maybe I could just die like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you.
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop.
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness.
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Please don't ever wake me from this.
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's allowed, please let me dream.
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, can I have a little bite of that?
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
間接キスなんてもう気にしないよ
I don't even care about an indirect kiss anymore.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, can I have a little bite of that?
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
……あなたが好きすぎて言い出せないよ
...I like you too much to say it.
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
Just one bite, I wanna taste it.
もうそろそろ気持ちが爆発しそうだよ
My feelings are about to explode.
抱きしめてみたいよ
I want to hold you tight.
……でも引かれたら立ち直れないし。。
...But if you pull away, I'll never recover.
臆病なの、変わらないや
I'm a coward, I never change.
目が合うだけで心臓が飛ぶ
Just our eyes meeting makes my heart leap.
せめて手だけは繋ぎたいの
At the very least, I want to hold your hand.
週末 弾けた恋模様
A sparkling love story on the weekend.
心が微熱どころではない
My heart has more than just a slight fever.
もう一度 夢に酔いしれて
Once more, intoxicated by this dream,
連れ出して！
Take me away!
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…？！
Maybe I could just die like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you.
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop.
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness.
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Please don't ever wake me from this.
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's allowed, please let me dream.
日が暮れるまで傍に居て
Stay by my side until the sun sets.
初キスはもう少し後で
Our first kiss can wait a little longer.
束縛は強めでOK？
Is it okay if I'm a bit possessive?
受け止めて 受け止めて
Accept me, accept me.
何も言わずに手を引いて
Without a word, take my hand.
そのまま遠くへ連れてって
And just take me far away.
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, anywhere.
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, can I have a little bite of that?
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to have one bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...But I couldn't bring myself to say it on our date today.
ひとくちだけ、食べたいの
Just one bite, I want a taste!
今、私は恋してるの！
Right now, I'm in love!
はい、ということで、みんなー！
Alright, and with that, everyone!
コンコンコンコン、こんあずきー！
Kon-kon-kon-kon, KonAZKi!
右手にマイク、左手に地図
A mic in my right hand, a map in my left,
あなたのハートをジャックしちゃうぞー！
I'm here to take over your heart!
あずきでーす！
I'm AZKi!
という事で、え、本日はAZKi 7th Birthday Live
So with that, uh, today is the AZKi 7th Birthday Live,
Sweet Pop Storyにお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Sweet Pop Story!
わーい、わいわいわい！
Yay! Whoo hoo!
始まった、始まった！
It's started, it's started!
え、なんと活動を始めて
Wow, since I began my activities,
7回目の誕生日を迎えることができました！
I'm able to celebrate my 7th birthday!
本当に本当にいつも応援してくれる開拓者のみんなのおかげで
It's really all thanks to my Pioneers who always support me
今日の日が、この日があると思っています。
that I'm able to be here today.
いつもありがとう！
Thank you always!
ということで、なんとね、もう今日は冒頭からじゃじゃーん！
And so, you know, today, right from the start... Ta-da!
新衣装お披露目でございまーす！
It's my new outfit reveal!
どうかな？どうかな？
What do you think? What do you think?
どう？どう？どうどうどうどう？はい！
How is it? How is it? Yes!
今回の、えー、新衣装のテーマはですね
The theme for this new outfit is...
ゆるふわ私服衣装となっております！
a fluffy and casual outfit!
可愛いでしょう？
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いでしょう？はい！
Isn't it cute? Yes!
ということでね、こういうね、なんか私服っぽくて
So, you know, I was thinking how nice it would be
可愛い衣装がいいなーって、ほしいなって思っていたので
to have a cute, casual-looking outfit,
今回お仕立てしていただきました！
so I had this one tailor-made!
そしてね、今日のこのライブステージもこの衣装に合わせて
And also, today's live stage was designed to match this outfit.
なんと、なんと、見てください皆さん
Would you look at that, everyone!
ちょっとお部屋っぽく
It's kind of like a room,
ちょっと、なんか、デートもできそうなステージになっております！
a stage where it feels like we could even go on a date!
ね、このね、新衣装にピッタリなステージになってます！
See? It's the perfect stage for this new outfit!
はい。ということで、今日はね、あの、この配信のハッシュタグ
Okay. And so, for today, the hashtag for this stream...
右上、こっち！これこれこれこれこれ！
is in the top right, over here! This one, this one!
#AZKi生誕ライブ2025 で
It's #AZKiBirthdayLive2025.
たくさんたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a ton with it!
え、スクショとか感想とか、全部全部あずきもチェックしますんで
Screenshots, your thoughts, AZKi will check every single one,
可愛いあずきをスクショするんだ。よろしくね！
so be sure to take screenshots of cute AZKi! Okay?
お願いします！
Please do!
え、そしてそして
And, and,
今日はですね、新衣装のお披露目だけではなく
today, it's not just the new outfit reveal,
重大発表もありますので
there's also a major announcement!
ぜひ最後まで見てください！よろしくね！
So please watch until the very end! Okay?
はい、ということでね
Alright, and with that...
早速ライブが始まったわけなんですが
So, the live show has just started,
ま、ちょっと今回は、Sweet Pop Storyということで
and this time, since it's "Sweet Pop Story,"
そう、物語風にね
we're doing it in a story-like style,
そう、デートなんかして見ちゃったり
like going on a date and all.
はい。
Yes.
してね、今日のライブ楽しんでいただけたらなと思います。
I hope you all enjoy today's live show.
で、1曲目は恋愛サーキュレーション
The first song was "Renai Circulation,"
そして、え、2曲目はひとくちちょうだい！っていうね、オリジナル曲でございました。
and the second was my original song, "Hitokuchi Choudai!"
どうだったかな？
How was it?
どうだった？可愛かった？
How was it? Was it cute?
と、いうことで
And with that,
ここから、なんとみんなお待ちかねの
From now on, what you've all been waiting for...
ゲストブロックになります！
...is the guest segment!
え、大好きなあのメンバーと
With that member I love,
可愛い曲を歌っちゃいますので
I'll be singing a cute song,
ぜひぜひ、楽しんでいただけたらと思います。
so please, I hope you enjoy it.
それじゃ行くよー！
Okay, here we go!
どうぞ！
Here it is!
浮つく甘い街の喧騒
The sweet, restless clamor of the city
故に感情線は渋滞
That's why the lines of emotion are congested
「僕に関係ない」とか言って
Saying, "It has nothing to do with me"
心模様 白く染まって
My heart's pattern is dyed white
だけどどうやったって釣り合わない
But no matter what I do, we're not a match
いたずらに笑う横顔に乾杯
A toast to your mischievous smiling profile
酸いも甘いもわからないの
I can't tell the sour from the sweet
きっと君の前では迷子
I'm surely lost in front of you
溶かしてはランデブー
Melting into a rendezvous
プラトニックになってく
It's becoming platonic
ほろ苦い期待 張り裂けてしまいそう
This bittersweet hope feels like it's about to burst
だから
So...
夢惑う
I wander in a dream
想いならば聞かせて
If that's how you feel, let me hear it
その声を
That voice of yours,
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
if I become dyed in your colors, if I'm dyed.
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Let your heart play, don't look away.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to think of you, I want to think of you.
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast.
今 混ざってしまえば 混ざってしまえば
If we could just mix together now, mix together.
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you, our gazes meet with love.
ロマンスは止まらない
The romance won't stop.
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神様 どうか今日は味方して
God, please be on my side today.
おかしな君は笑って
You, so peculiar, laughed,
逆さま世界が顔出して
and an upside-down world showed its face.
夢ならまだ覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up yet.
心模様 赤に染まってく
My heart's pattern is being dyed red.
冷静沈着では どう頑張ったってない
Being calm and composed won't get me anywhere.
大体 視界に居ない
You're usually not even in my sight.
ちょっと late なスターリーナイト
A slightly late starry night
最低な昨日にさえ さよなら言いたいよな
I want to say goodbye even to the worst yesterday
甘いおまじないかけられてしまいそう
It feels like a sweet spell is about to be cast on me
だから
So
この夜を越えてゆけ
Go on and get through this night
響かせて
Let it resonate
その想いを
Those feelings of yours
君に染まってしまえば
If I become dyed in your color
Ah-
君だけ想っていたいな
I just want to think of you
Ah-
君に染まってしまえば
If I'm dyed in your colors
染まってしまえば
dyed in your colors
心揺らせ 余所見してないで
Let your heart sway, don't look away
想っていたいな
I want to think of you
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast
今伝えてしまえ
Tell me now
伝えてしまえば
If you just tell me
君と重なって
Overlapping with you
視線が愛 相まって
our gazes and love intertwine
Oh-
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step
神さま
Oh God
どうか今日は味方して
please be on my side today
「スキになれ！
"Fall for me!
ぜったいスキになれ！」
You have to fall for me!"
おまじない
A magic spell
アナタごとデコレーション
a decoration with all of you
朝からビターなキモチ
A bitter feeling since this morning
だって知らない表情[かお]で笑った
Because you smiled with a face I don't know
ちょっと髪に触れたりしちゃって
You even touched her hair
なんでハナの下伸ばしてんの！？
Why are you grinning like that!?
どんどん膨れてくジェラシー
My jealousy just keeps on swelling
スフレみたいに甘くないよ
It's not sweet like a soufflé
胸いっぱいに溢れちゃって
It's overflowing in my chest
ダメダメ！気付かれちゃうよ！
No, no! They'll notice!
バレないように…
So they won't find out...
でも気付いて！
But please notice!
フクザツな乙女心
A maiden's complicated heart
「スキになれ！
"Fall for me!
ぜったいスキになれ！」
You have to fall for me!"
おまじない
A magic spell
アナタごとデコレーション
a decoration with all of you
恋心ちょっとキャラメリゼ
Let's caramelize this budding love a bit
焦がしたらきっとスキにさせるから！
Once it's scorched, I'll make you fall for me!
今日は朝からちょっとラッキー
Today's been a bit lucky since morning
あくびこらえた変顔見ちゃった
I saw the funny face you made holding back a yawn
肩叩きながら「おはよ」
Tapping your shoulder saying "Morning"
言えたらもっと…ああ！もうイケナイ！
If I could say more... Ah! I can't!
ふぅ…ちょっと落ち着いて？
Phew... Calm down a little?
モンテしすぎて零れちゃうよ
If I whip it too much, it'll spill over
「なにしてんの？」ってほっぺツンツン
"What are you doing?" you poke my cheek
いきなりまさかの不意打ち禁止～！！
A sudden surprise attack is forbidden!!
メレンゲハート
Meringue heart
耳までキューイル
blushing to my ears
アツいのは私だけ？
Am I the only one feeling this?
メレンゲハート 耳までキューイール
Meringue heart, flushed to my ears
アツいのは私だけ？
Am I the only one feeling this heat?
スキすぎる!
I love you too much!
あぁ…スキすぎる!
Ahh... I love you too much!
ココロから スペシャリテのアイラブユー
From my heart, a spécialité I love you
恋心もっとタブラージュ
My loving heart, let's tablage it even more
溶けたならハート型にグラッセしよ
If it melts, let's glacé it into a heart shape.
アナタにだけ 教えてあげる
I'll only tell you,
このキモチのヒミツ
the secret of these feelings.
「ダイスキだよ」
"I love you."
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall for me! You have to fall for me!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating all of you.
このキモチ ずっとア・ラ・カルト
These feelings, always à la carte.
おすそわけ ココロごとデコレーション
A little share, decorating your whole heart.
恋心いっぱいプレゼント
A present full of love.
届いたら 私ごと召し上がれ♪
When it arrives, please enjoy me as well ♪
Lalala...♪
なーにしよっか練習中
Practicing what to do
しれっとこそっと準備進行
Casually and secretly, the prep is underway
心境 緊張で焦る
I'm nervous and feeling flustered
言わんけどつよつよアリでしょ？
I won't say it, but I'm super strong, right?
元気配るから待っちょって
I'm sharing my energy, so just wait
そうやって成長する子です
That's how this kid grows
いいかな
Is that okay?
ゆるポンでOK?
Is a lazy 'pon' okay?
いちにーさん
One, two, three
テンパっちゃってOK?
Is it okay to panic?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started
ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me,
I want you to praise me.
ほめてくれたら
If you praise me,
2割増しでがんばる
I'll try 20% harder.
見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me,
I want you to watch me.
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows when showered with praise.
もお
More!
なぁーんにも出てこない
Nothing's coming out.
頭ん中真っ白だ
My mind's a total blank.
さっぱりだ うんうんうん あれ？
Completely blank...uh-oh, huh?
まっいっか
Oh well.
凸凹な情緒 提供中
My bumpy emotions are on display,
ぽかんとして何しちょんの
spacing out, what am I doing?
こんなんが通常のわたし
This is the usual me.
いいでしょ
It's fine, right?
それではOK?
So, is that OK?
いちにーさん
One, two, three.
落ち着きOK?
Calm and collected? OK?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started!
どうしたらいいの?どうしたらいいの?
What should I do? What should I do?
どうすればみんなハッピーで笑顔バッチリ
How can I make everyone happy with perfect smiles?
こちらへどうぞ こちらへどうぞ
This way please, this way please.
押さず慌てず並んで合図です
No pushing, no rushing, line up for the signal.
もー
C'mon!
聞こえてる?
Can you hear me?
(みゃみゃみゃみゃ)
(Meow meow meow meow)
楽しんでる?
Are you having fun?
(ぽんぽんぽん)
(Pon pon pon)
こっちだよ
Over here!
少し眠いな 少し眠いな
I'm a little sleepy, a little sleepy.
また明日食べて寝て 今は成長期
I'll eat and sleep tomorrow again, I'm in my growth spurt.
夢を見たいな 夢を見たいな
I want to have a dream, I want to have a dream.
どうぞくれぐれも あの..今後も
By all means, um... from now on too.
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me, I want you to praise me.
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll try 20% harder.
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me.
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who thrives on lots of praise.
またね
See ya!
sweet night, sweet time...
作詞・作曲・編曲：佐高陵平(Hifumi,inc.)
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Sako Ryohei (Hifumi,inc.)
sweet night, sweet time...
そっと陽の沈む茜の空
The sun softly sets into the glowing sky.
やっと目覚めたきみに挨拶
I finally woke up and said hello to you.
えっと明日は休みだから
Um, tomorrow's a day off, so
一晩中きみと一緒に
I'll be with you all night long.
sweet night, sweet time...
眠くないよ 眠く無いの
I'm not sleepy, not sleepy at all
sweet night, sweet time...
まだまだ遊びたい
I still want to play more
sweet night, sweet time...
話したいよ 話し足んないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Because in a dream, it's not enough
今夜は…
Tonight...
寝なーい 眠らない
We won't sleep, we're not sleeping
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching the rhythm with you
昼夜逆転を楽しもうの
Let's enjoy turning night into day
今だけ寝なーい 眠らない
Just for now, we won't sleep
星の中散歩して
Strolling among the stars
夜がどうか明けないように
Hoping that the night won't end
いつまでも
Forever and ever
sweet night, sweet time...
いつまでも
Forever and ever
sweet night, sweet time...
きっと話すのも笑うのも
Surely, both talking and laughing...
もっと誰かと繋がるため
...are for connecting more with someone
ちょっと俯いたきみへ向けて
For you, who was looking down a little
一晩中 歌ってほしい
I want you to sing all night long
一晩中 歌ってもいい
It's fine to sing all night long
sweet night, sweet time...
眠らないよ 眠らないの
I won't sleep, not sleeping at all
sweet night, sweet time...
夜ごと遊びたい
I want to play every night
sweet night, sweet time...
喋りたいよ 喋りたんないの
I want to chat, I haven't chatted enough
sweet night, sweet time...
きみと朝まで
With you, until morning
月も知らない
Even the moon doesn't know
ナイショ話を
our secret talks
パジャマのままで
While still in our pajamas
お願い
please
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Because in a dream, it's not enough
もう少し…
Just a little longer...
寝なーい 眠らない
We won't sleep, we're not sleeping
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching the rhythm with you
昼夜逆転を楽しもうの
Let's enjoy turning night into day
今だけ寝なーい 眠らない
Just for now, we won't sleep
白む空見送って
Watching the brightening sky
夜を越えよう
Let's get through the night,
また明日もここで会おう
and meet here again tomorrow
good night, good time...
また明日
See you tomorrow
good night, good time...
また明日
See you tomorrow
good night, good time...
というわけで、ゲストブロックをお送りしました！
And with that, we've just brought you the guest segment!
どうだったかな？どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい。ということでゲストパートなんですが、
Yes. So, about the guest part...
ここまでを振り返ると
Looking back so far,
えー、いろはちゃんと、え、心予報をお届けしました。
with Iroha-chan, we performed 'Kokoro Yohou'.
なんとね、いろはちゃんのあの新衣装3Dでね、
And what's more, it was with Iroha-chan's new 3D outfit.
一緒にこれは、あずいろてぇてぇ。
Together, this was our 'AZIro TeeTee'.
あずいろてぇてぇをしたいと思って、え、一緒にね歌ってみたい
I really wanted to have that TeeTee moment, so we performed
って思って出した心予報をちょっと踊って一緒にこの新衣装で
'Kokoro Yohou' and danced in our new outfits.
あずいろてぇてぇしました。
It was our AZIro TeeTee moment.
どうだった？どうだった？よかったでしょう？
How was it? How was it? It was good, right?
え、そして、え、次はラミィちゃんと
And then, next up with Lamy-chan,
初恋パティシエールという
we did 'Hatsukoi Patissier'.
ラミィたんのオリ曲をね、
It's Lamy-tan's original song,
もうこの、このライブのテーマに絶対合うと思って、
and I thought it'd be a perfect fit for this live's theme,
一緒に歌わせていただきました。
so we sang it together.
可愛かった。
It was so cute.
え、そしてそして、え、団長と、褒めの日！
And, and then, with Danchou, 'Homenobi'!
これはね、ずっとずっとAZKi一緒に団長と褒めの日を
This was my dream, to sing 'Homenobi' with Danchou.
歌うのが夢だったんで
It's always been a dream of mine.
もうこのライブで実現するぞと思って、
So I decided to make it happen in this live.
え、褒めの日で成長していきたいと、思います。
I want to grow through 'Homenobi'. I think.
え、そしてそして、え、わためぇと一緒に、
And, and then, with Watame,
え、わためぇのオリジナル曲、Sweet Night, Sweet Time!を歌わせていただきました。
we sang her original song, 'Sweet Night, Sweet Time!'.
もうこれもね、今回のコンセプトにめちゃくちゃ合う、
This song also fits this concert's concept perfectly.
わためぇとこの曲一緒に歌いたいなと思って、
I really wanted to sing this song with Watame,
え、選曲しました。
so I chose it.
どうだったかな？
How was it?
いやー嬉しいね。ホロメンのオリ曲歌ったりできるの
Ah, I'm so happy. Getting to sing Holomems' original songs
本当にライブならではっていう感じで
is something you can only do at a live concert.
えー、お送りしましたが、まだまだゲストパート続きますんで、
So, that's what we performed, but the guest part isn't over yet!
え、セトリストのAZKiさんにもご注目ください。
So please enjoy the rest of the setlist I've prepared.
ということで、まだまだゲストパート、行くぞ！
And so, with that, the guest segment continues! Let's go!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Waving my tail, scouting you out
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Let's encounter more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we all get together, we're the strongest!
文化祭が始まる
The school festival's starting
最大規模でいきたいの
I want to make it the biggest ever
君も参加してよね
You should join in too!
ネットチケット無制限
Online tickets are unlimited
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal will be surprised
キャスト足んない 大焦り
Not enough cast members, I'm in a huge panic!
ワンワン泣いちゃう うう
I'm gonna cry, boo-hoo...
本番間近 胃はキリキリ
The show's almost here, my stomach's in knots
運営の予算はギリギリ
The operating budget is razor-thin
すねちゃうぞ 泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna pout! I'm gonna cry!
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number, beep beep beep beep beep
「イケてる子を用意して」
"Get me some cool girls."
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェック！スカウター！
Cute girl, check! Scouter!
超超！超委員長！美少女ゲットだぜ☆
Super, super! Super class president! Got a cute girl☆
美少女捕まえた☆
I've caught a cute girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Make it a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this
尻尾ふってスカウト
Wag my tail and scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encounter more cute girls
集っちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather, we're the strongest!
あー無駄足しんどいわ
Ah, this wasted trip is tiring
どうしようもない焦燥感
An unbearable feeling of impatience
タイムリミットはあとちょっと！？
The time limit is almost up!?
ここらでもういっちょ！
Let's go for one more around here!
美味しいころね食べたら
After eating a delicious Korone
犬に金棒最強よ
a dog with a metal club is the strongest!
東西南北駆け回り
Running around east, west, south, and north
まだ見ぬあの子探しだせ！
Find that girl I haven't seen yet!
わんわん鳴いちゃう わぉん
I'll start barking, woof!
呼んだらどこでも駆けつけます！
If you call, I'll come running anywhere!
いい子がいたら、教えてね
If there's a good girl, let me know
噛んじゃうぞ
I'll bite you!
甘えちゃうぞ
I'll get spoiled by you!
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number, pi pi pi pi pi
「イケてる子が見つかった？」
"Found a cool girl?"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェック！ スカウター！
Cute girl, check! Scouter!
超超！超委員長！美少女ゲットだぜ☆
Super, super! Super class president! Got a cute girl☆
美少女捕まえた☆
I've caught a cute girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Make it a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this
尻尾ふってスカウト
Wag my tail and scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encounter more cute girls
集っちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather, we're the strongest!
自薦他薦は問いません
Self-recommendations and others' are welcome
「私、君を待ってるよ」
"I'm waiting for you."
へへっ
Hehe
うーっ
Ugh...
あーっ もう
Ah... Geez
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't mess up, right?
真っ赤なハート差し出して
Offering up a bright red heart
そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
that's just a delusion, isn't it?
そっちはどう思ってんの？
"What do you think?"
言いかけてしまう 無理みたい
I almost say it... it seems impossible
こんなんじゃってわかってんだ 思うほどにハマっていくんだ
I know it's like this, the more I think, the more I fall
頑張りたい あたしに期待 ぎゅーだってしたいかも かもん
I want to do my best, I have hope, maybe even hug, c'mon
ちょっとは変われていますか？
Have I changed a little?
足りないとこばっかだけど
Though I'm full of flaws
ポンでコツでドジじゃない あたしだったら
If I wasn't so clumsy and awkward
きみはだめだよね？
you still wouldn't want me, right?
ねえもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, no way, I can't mess this up
もうやだやだ 踊ってベイビーダンス
No way, just dance, baby dance
あたしはまだ諦めない
I won't give up yet
でもでも全然だめかも
but maybe, maybe it's completely hopeless
だってベイビーダンス
'Cause it's a baby dance
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
Because, baby dance, I can't do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because, baby dance, I can't express myself
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
I want to be cuter,
どうしたらいいかわかんないし
but I don't know what to do
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't mess up, right?
あ～やっちまった こんなはずじゃ
Ah, I messed up, it wasn't supposed to be like this
どうしてどうして わかっているのに
Why, oh why, even though I know it
見せたくないとこ避けちゃって 無理無理
I avoid the parts I don't want to show. No way, no way.
でも期待はしたいな いいですか？
But I want to have hope. Is that okay?
ポンもコツもドジも全部あたしなんだよ
My clumsiness and mistakes are all part of me
ちゃんと見ていてほしい
I want you to watch me closely
ねえもうやだやだ ぐずって後悔
Oh no, I hate this, whining and regretting
もうやだやだ 回ってベイビーダンス
I hate this, spinning around, baby dance
だめなあたし塗り替えたい
I want to change this useless me
でもでも 全然だめかも
But, but, maybe I'm completely hopeless
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
Because, baby dance, I can't do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because, baby dance, I can't express myself
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
I want to be cuter,
どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
but I don't know what to do
まだまだいけるかな
Can I still keep going?
まだまだ言えるかな
Can I still say it?
まだまだできるかな
Can I still do it?
まだまだ…うぅ…
Still... ugh...
ポンでコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかだって
Even if I'm clumsy, awkward, and not good enough
きっとやめないんだ
I'm sure I won't quit
ポンでコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかだって
Even if I'm clumsy, awkward, and not good enough
見ていてほしい
I want you to watch me
ういぇーい！
Yeah!
ねえもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Oh no, I hate this, I can't mess up
もうやだやだ 踊ってベイビーダンス
I hate this, dancing the baby dance
あたしはまだ諦めない
I won't give up yet
ほらほら 全然だめじゃない
See, see, I'm not hopeless at all
だってベイビーダンス うまくできるから
Because, baby dance, I can do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられるから
Because, baby dance, I can express myself
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to be cuter,
どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I can always do my best
だってベイビーダンス 君に届くまで
Because, baby dance, until it reaches you
だってベイビーダンス 君に会えるまで
Because, baby dance, until I can meet you
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to be cuter,
どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I can always do my best
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't mess up, right?
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Surprise
Service
We are スティーレ!!
We are STILE!!
さあ扉を開けて
Come on, open the door
未知なるパラダイス
To an unknown paradise
体験しよう おいでYOU
Let's experience it, come on YOU!
そうキミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
That's right, a mysterious oasis is waiting for you
ほっこり日常に ちょっぴりSpice
A little Spice for your cozy daily life
くるん くるん かき混ぜちゃうんだ
Swirl, swirl, we'll mix it all up
ぐーるん ぐーるん 当店自慢のフレイバー
Stir, stir, our shop's special Flavor
サービス サービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, it's reward Time
おもてなし ココロこめて
Hospitality from the bottom of our hearts
Welcome to…
Welcome to...
わーい！ 私たちと一緒に
Yay! Together with us
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
A dazzling wonder daydream
愛情マシマシ
Full of affection
煩悩ナデナデ
Patting worldly desires
誠心誠意つとめます
We'll serve you with all our hearts
YES! キミの元気チャージに
Yes! To charge up your energy,
ひと役かえるかな
I wonder if I can play a part?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも
This kind of feeling, and that kind of feeling,
意外と悪くないでしょ?
isn't it surprisingly not so bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend!
きゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんちぱんちぱんち
Thump, thump, thump, a punch, punch, punch to your heart!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend!
お口にあいますか？
Is it to your liking?
お口にあうといいな♪
I hope it's to your liking!
ボナペティート?
Bon appétit?
ぼなぺてぃーと?
千客ばんらーい！
Welcome one and all!
ちょっと、なんか、不本意ながらも
Well, somewhat reluctantly,
いつだって需要は斜め上
the demand is always unexpected.
そんじゃいっか、ホントのわたしは
Oh well, the real me
シークレットモードで 営業スイッチオン
is in secret mode, with business switch ON!
くるん くるん かきまぜてもっと
Twirl, twirl, stir it up even more.
ぐーるん ぐーるん キミ仕様のフレイバー
Spin, spin, a flavor made just for you.
サービス サービス 極上タイム
Service, service, it's a sublime time.
癒しとは かくあるべき
This is how healing should be.
Welcome to… わーい！わたしたちのお店に
Welcome to... Yay! To our shop!
本日もようこそ
Welcome today as well!
おかえり待ってた リピートうれしいな
Welcome back, I waited. Glad you're a repeat customer!
店員一同 歓迎！
All of us staff welcome you!
YES! キミのお疲れさまに
Yes! To reward your hard work,
ピッタリのレシピで
with the perfect recipe.
こーいうのどうかな あーいうのアリかな
How about this? Is that one okay?
よろこんでもらえてるかな
I wonder if you're happy with it?
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Small
Strange
Serious
Selfish
Super Girl
We are スティーレ!!
We are Stile!!
さあ扉を開けて 愉快なパラダイス
Now, open the door to a delightful paradise.
怖がらずにおいで
Come on without fear.
そう、いつも通りの毎日に
Yes, to your usual everyday,
イロドリと アソビゴコロ
adding color and a playful spirit.
召し上がれ
Please enjoy!
ブレンド・S
Blend-S!
Welcome to… わーい！わたしたちと一緒に
Welcome to... Yay! Together with us!
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
A dazzling wonder daydream!
愛情マシマシ
Full of affection,
煩悩ナデナデ
patting worldly desires,
誠心誠意つとめます
we'll serve you with all our hearts!
いぇーす！キミの元気チャージに
Yes! To charge up your energy,
ひと役かえるかな
I wonder if I can play a part?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも
This kind of feeling, and that kind of feeling,
意外と悪くないでしょ？
isn't it surprisingly not so bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend!
きゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんちぱんちぱんち
Thump, thump, thump, a punch, punch, punch to your heart!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to make a blend.
お口にあいますか？
Is it to your liking?
お好み聞かせてね
Tell me what you like.
お口にあうといいな♪
I hope it's to your liking♪
というわけで、引き続きゲストブロックをお送りしました。
And with that, we've just brought you the guest block.
どうだったかな？
How was it?
このあとはですね、重大発表もございますので、ぜひ最後まで見てねー！
After this, there's a major announcement, so please watch until the very end!
はい。そんなゲストブロックの後半なんですが、え、コロさんと、かわいこチェックでしっぽフリフリしました。
Right. For the latter half of the guest block, with Koro-san, we did a cuteness check and wagged our tails.
そしてみこちと、ベイビーダンスをお送りしました。
And with Miko-chi, we performed Baby Dance.
なんか私服衣装でね、シナジーあったんじゃないかなって思います。
We had great synergy in our casual outfits, don't you think?
そしてそして、ふわもこちゃんと、ボナペティート♡Sをお届けしました。
And, and, with FuwaMoco-chan, we brought you Bon Appétit♡S.
ふわもこちゃんとね、一緒にね、こうやって3Dライブしたいなと思ってたので、もう念願、念願かなってあずきのね、やりたいことを全部全部詰め込んだゲストパートでございました。
I'd wanted to do a 3D live with FuwaMoco-chan for so long, so it was a guest part packed with all my dreams and everything I wanted to do.
はい、ということで、ま、重大発表もあるんですけど、
Alright, so, there's a major announcement coming up,
その前に皆さん、あのお知らせがございます。
but before that, everyone, we have that announcement!
あずき誕生日記念2025グッズ販売告知！
The AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 Merchandise Sale Announcement!
こちらをご覧ください！
Please take a look!
うおー！今回もだだだだーんと盛りだくさんでございます。
Whoa! This time, too, it's an incredibly jam-packed lineup!
え、今回イラストはD福先生に描いていただきました。ありがとうございます。
The illustration this time was drawn by D-fuku-sensei. Thank you very much.
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう。まずはこちら。
Now then, let's take a look at the details. First up is this!
だだだだ！抱き枕カバー！
Ta-da! A body pillow cover!
ということで、今回のゆるふわな、え、私服の衣装で寝転がっているAZKiの抱き枕カバーが出ます！うわー！
So for this time's soft and fluffy casual outfit, a body pillow cover of a lounging AZKi is being released! Whoa!
まさかグッズになるとは思いもいりませんでしたが、ぜひチェックしてください。
I never thought this would become merch. Please be sure to check it out.
え、続いてはこちら。
Next up is this!
え、缶バッジセット。
A can badge set.
えー、こちらね、ハートの形をした缶バッジとなっております。え、キラキラのホログラム仕様となっておりますので、いっぱい、いっぱいね、つけてほしいなと思います。
This is a heart-shaped can badge set. It has a sparkling hologram finish, so I hope you'll wear them a lot.
続いてはこちら。
Next up is this!
え、開拓者ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
A Pioneer Plush Keychain!
え、ということで、ホロライブフレンズ with Uのね、AZKiと大体同じぐらいのね、ちっちゃいサイズになってますんで、一緒に持ち歩いてもらえるようなサイズ感となっておりますので、一緒にね、あずぬいと、え、開拓者ぬいで、お出かけしてほしいなと思います。
So, this is about the same small size as AZKi's hololive friends with u plushie, so I hope you'll take both the 'Azunui' and the Pioneer plushie out with you.
続いてはこちら。
Next up is this!
開拓者アイマスク！
A Pioneer Eye Mask!
ま、今回の抱き枕カバーと一緒に、もう安眠できるね、グッズをね、え、ご用意いたしましたので、こちらもぜひ、え、寝る時に
Paired with the body pillow cover, we've prepared some merch for a good night's sleep. So please use this when you go to sleep.
使ってほしいなと思います。
I hope you'll use it.
え、そして続いてはこちら。
And next up is this.
ASMRボイス。
An ASMR voice pack.
ボイスタイトルはAZKiのわがままをきいて。
The title is "Listen to AZKi's Selfish Requests."
というね、ちょっとAZKiがちょっとしたわがままを言って
It's a voice pack where I act a little selfish
ね、君をね、デートに誘うシチュエーションとなっております。
and ask you out on a date.
今回のね、このゆるふわ私服衣装のAZKiを思い浮かべて聞いてください。
Please listen to it while imagining AZKi in this casual outfit.
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます。こちら。
And there's also a full set purchase bonus. Here it is.
え、なんと数量限定版は、AZKiの直筆サイン入り
The limited edition version includes a cheki-style bromide card
特典ASMRボイス、タイトルは「寝起きのAZKiと」
and a bonus ASMR voice pack titled "With AZKi Who Just Woke Up."
ということで、え、こちらね
So, with that said,
抱き枕カバーの、なんかちょっと裏面のイラストをねイメージしたシチュエーションと
this is a scenario based on the illustration on the back of the pillow cover.
なっておりますので、こちらも一緒に楽しんでいただけたらなと思います。
I hope you enjoy it along with the rest.
そしてね、数量限定がなくなり次第、え、箔押しの複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと
Once the limited edition runs out, it will be replaced with a foil-stamped replica signature card
特典ASMRボイス、同様の「寝起きのAZKiと」となっておりますので、よろしくお願いします。
and the same bonus ASMR voice, "With AZKi Who Just Woke Up." So please look forward to it.
え、改めてフルセットはこちらとなります。じゃん。
To reiterate, the full set is this. Ta-da!
いやー、いっぱいね、ありますね。
Wow, there's so much!
買うならね、やっぱね、フルセットがいいですよ。みんな、
If you're going to buy it, the full set is the way to go, everyone.
よろしくね、この後。
Please check it out later.
はい、そしてさらにタレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典といたしまして
And as a full set bonus for the talent premium goods...
去年から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚つきます。
...you get one card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game, which was released last year.
え、カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります。
The card is only available to those who purchase from the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできるキーカード
The bonus is a key card that lets you show off your favorite member.
推しホロメンカードでございます。
It's an Oshi-holomen card.
え、カードの詳細や遊び方については、ホームページをご確認ください。
For details on the card and how to play, please check the homepage.
え、同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなりますので、ご了承ください。
Please note that the included card is the Japanese version only.
以上、AZKi誕生日記念2025のグッズ情報でした。
That was all the information on the AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 goods.
みんな買ってね、ぜひ。よろしくお願いします。
Everyone, please buy them! I'm counting on you.
ということで、お待たせいたしました。
And with that, thank you for waiting.
さらに、重大発表ございます。
Furthermore, I have a major announcement.
それではお待たせいたしました。こちらをご覧ください。
Now then, thank you for waiting. Please take a look.
重大発表
Major Announcement
2025.11.05
Re://Birth
Re://Start
AZKi New EP
2025.11.05 ON SALE
7/1 21:00より 各種CDショップ・hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPにて予約受付開始
Pre-orders start 7/1 at 21:00 at various CD shops and the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP
はい、ということで、AZKiの新しいEP「リスタート」と「リバース」が
Yes, that's right! AZKi's new EPs, "Re://Start" and "Re://Birth," will be released
11月5日に
on November 5th!
にリリースすることが決定しましたー！
has been decided for release!
今回は初めてとなる2作同時リリースとなっております。
This time, it's our first simultaneous release of two works.
この後21時よりホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップと
From 9 PM tonight, on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP
全国のCDショップで予約が開始されます。
and at CD shops nationwide, pre-orders will begin.
そして1枚目のリスタートには、
And the first EP, 'Re:Start,'
あずきの新しい魅力が詰まった新曲4曲。
has four new songs packed with my new charms.
2枚目のリバースには、イノナカミュージック時代の楽曲4曲の
The second EP, 'Re:Birth,' includes 4 songs from my INNK Music era
リアレンジバージョンが収録されます。
that have been rearranged.
そしてCD限定特典として、それぞれボーナストラックに
As a CD-exclusive bonus, each version has a bonus track:
すいちゃんと歌ったThe Last Frontierが1種類ずつ収録されます。
a version of 'The Last Frontier,' which I sang with Suichan.
また、通常版には限定特典として
Also, the standard edition comes with a limited bonus:
ランダムアナザージャケットが1枚ついてきます。
one random alternate jacket will be included.
なんと、こちらには数量限定で私の直筆サイン入りが入っているかもとのことです。
And get this, a limited number might even have my autograph!
え、各CDショップでの購入特典はこちらです！
Here are the purchase bonuses for each CD shop!
特典の絵柄は後日発表します。
The artwork for the bonuses will be announced later.
さらに、ホロライブオフィシャルショップではセットになったコンプリート盤を発売します！
Furthermore, a complete edition set will be sold on the hololive OFFICIAL SHOP!
えー、コンプリート盤には、ここでしか手に入らないたくさんの特典もついております。
The complete edition comes with many bonuses you can only get here.
え、数にこちら限りがございますので、お早めにー。
These are limited in quantity, so please get yours early.
そして1点。え、ホロライブオフィシャルショップのアルバム購入について注意点がございます。
One more thing. A notice about album purchases from the hololive OFFICIAL SHOP.
完全生産限定コンプリート盤は、発売日でのお届けとなりますので、
The limited complete edition will be delivered on the release date,
EP以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入できません。
so it can't be purchased with merchandise other than the EP.
通常版は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが、
The standard edition can be bought with other merch,
店頭販売日以降のお届けになる可能性がありますので、
but it may be delivered after the in-store release date.
こちらご注意ください。
Please be aware of this.
詳しくは販売サイトの注意点をご確認ください。
For details, please check the notes on the sales site.
はい。そして
Okay! And...
最後に、もう一つお知らせあります。
I have one final announcement.
今回発表したこのニューEP「リスタート」の中から
From the new EP 'Re:Start' that I just announced,
「未来カンパネラ」という楽曲を、本日24時にデジタルリリースします！
the song 'Mirai Campanella' will be digitally released tonight at 24:00 JST!
わー！新曲だ！
Yay! It's a new song!
配信終了後にはミュージックビデオもプレミア公開しちゃいます
After the stream ends, the music video will also premiere,
ということで、ぜひチェックしてください！
so please be sure to check it out!
わー！いっぱい情報がありましたがみんなついてこれましたか？
Wow! That was a lot of info. Did you all keep up?
はい。
Yes.
え、ということで、ライブも、え、次の曲で最後になります。
And with that, the live show will end after the next song.
え、最後はね、あずきの新しい曲を聴いていただきたいと思います。
For the finale, I'd like you to listen to a new song from me.
それでは
Well then,
聴いてください
please listen.
未来カンパネルラ
Mirai Campanella.
もっと
More
鏡よ 教えて
Mirror, mirror, tell me,
私の証は
where is the proof of my existence,
どこにあるのだろう
where could it be?
分からない 分からないよ
I don't know, I just don't know.
周りと比べたってさ
Comparing myself to others
虚しくなるだけ
only makes me feel empty.
あぁ ノイズが
Ah, the noise,
海鳴りのように
like the roar of the sea,
ナミダを奪う
steals my tears.
切り取った風景を
Let's use the scenery I've captured
道しるべにしよう
as my guide.
そうだ
That's right,
傷ついた感情も
I'll take my hurt feelings
連れて行くから
along with me.
そっと響くカンパネルラ
A gently echoing campanella,
新しい未来を感じてる
I'm feeling a new future.
怖くたって
Even if I'm scared,
進むしかないでしょう？
I have to move forward, right?
遠くまで
Far away,
届け この祈りよ 光となれ
let this prayer reach, and become light.
もっと もっと
More and more,
少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
even if it's little by little, the answer that is "me".
もっと
More
もっと…
More...
夜空よ 教えて
Oh night sky, tell me,
私の証は
can the proof of my existence
輝けるのかな
truly shine?
見つけたい 見つけたいよ
I want to find it, I really do.
誰かの決めたレールは
The path someone else laid out
苦しくなるだけ
only brings me pain.
ねぇ ノイズも 力に変えるよ
Hey, I'll turn even the noise into strength,
ココロに誓う
I swear to my heart.
錆びついた運命の 歯車を回そう
Let's turn the rusted gears of fate.
ほら 着飾った感情は
Look, these dressed-up emotions,
脱ぎ捨てるから
I'm casting them off.
そっと紡ぐシンフォニア
A gently woven sinfonia,
叶えたい 願いを信じてる
I believe in the wishes I want to grant.
胸を張って
I have to sing with my chest held high,
歌うしかないでしょう？
there's no other choice, right?
全力で
With all my might,
やがて希望の歌に 変わる日まで
until the day it becomes a song of hope.
もっと もっと
More and more,
悩みながらでいい すべてが宝物
it's okay to struggle. Everything is a treasure.
いつの日か
If someday
この声を受け取ってくれたなら
you can receive this voice,
この言葉を君に
I'll give these words to you:
「もう大丈夫、一人じゃない」
"It's okay now, you're not alone."
強い想いを繋ぐよ
I'll connect these strong feelings.
一歩踏み出してみた
I took a step forward,
優しく世界は微笑む
and the world smiled gently.
The world smiles gently
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて
Letting my throbbing heart take over
さあ行こう
Let's go,
そっと響くカンパネラ
the campanella gently rings
新しい 未来を感じてる
I'm feeling a new future
怖くたって
Even if I'm scared,
進むしかないでしょ？
I have to move forward, right?
遠くまで
To a faraway place
届けこの祈りよ
May this prayer reach,
光となれ
and become light
もっと もっと
More and more
少しずつでもいい
Little by little is fine,
「私」という答えを
the answer that is "me."
もっと
More,
more
もっと…
More...
ごめん、待った？
Sorry, have you been waiting?
ごめんね。ライブ終わった後、
Sorry. After the show,
マネージャーさんに呼ばれちゃって。
my manager called for me.
もちろん打ち上げもあったけど、
There was a wrap party, of course,
君と会うためにキャンセルしたんだからね。
but I cancelled it to meet you.
改めて、今日はライブに来てくれてありがとう。
Again, thank you for coming to my show today.
アリーナ席の右の方にいたよね？
You were in the arena seats on the right, right?
ちゃんと見つけたよ。
I found you.
実は今日花火大会なんだって。
Actually, there's a fireworks festival today.
こんな都会で花火上がるのロマンチックだな。
Fireworks in a city like this is so romantic.
ねぇ、見てみて。
Hey, look, look.
今日のライブのキービジュアルだよ。
That's the key visual for today's show.
もしかしたら、ここでも流れてたのかな？
I wonder if it was playing here too?
ついさっきのことだから、
It just happened,
ちょっと恥ずかしいよ。
so it's a little embarrassing.
でも、とっても楽しかったな。
But it was so much fun.
あっ、雨？
Ah, is it raining?
どうしよう。
What should I do?
私、傘持ってないよ。
I don't have an umbrella.
あ、傘、持ってきてくれたんだ。
Ah, an umbrella... You brought one for me.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
かっこいいじゃん。
You're so cool.
でも、傘一本しかないってことは
But, since there's only one umbrella,
これって…相合傘だよね？
this means... we're sharing it, right?
私、相合傘って初めてで…
This is my first time sharing an umbrella...
これってさぁ…
So, this is...
バイバイ。
Bye bye.
ドキドキするね。
My heart's pounding.
あ、雨が止んだ。
Oh, the rain has stopped.
通り雨だったのかな？
Was that a passing shower?
なんか雨止んで嬉しいような
The rain stopped, and I feel kind of happy,
悲しいような。
but also kind of sad.
もっと君と相合傘したかったなー。
I wanted to share an umbrella with you longer.
なんてね。
Just kidding.
雨も止んだし、
The rain stopped,
雨で人通りも少なくなったしさ、
and there are fewer people around now.
グリコゲームでもしようよ。
Let's play the Glico game.
ここからスタートね。
We'll start from here.
行くよ。
Ready?
じゃんけんぽん。
Rock, paper, scissors.
やったー！私の勝ち。
Yay! I win.
ちーよーこーれーいーと。
Cho-co-la-te.
ちょっと、何？にやにやして見てるの？
Hey, what? Why are you grinning at me?
え？かわいいって？
Huh? You think I'm cute?
もう、ちょっと恥ずかしいからやめてよ。
Come on, stop it. It's a little embarrassing.
次、行くよ。
Next round.
じゃんけんぽん。
Rock, paper, scissors.
プリート。
Pu-ri-to.
だから、ちょっとにやにや止めてってば。
I told you to stop grinning.
次、行くよ。
Next round.
じゃんけんぽん。
Rock, paper, scissors.
ぱーいーなーつーぷーる。
Pi-ne-ap-ple.
もう、じゃんけん弱すぎだよ。
You're so bad at rock-paper-scissors.
絶対、わざと負けてるでしょ。
You're definitely losing on purpose, aren't you?
もう、いい加減にしてよね。
Oh, give me a break.
え？何？
Huh? What is it?
こっち来てって？
You want me to come over?
どこ行くの？
Where are we going?
何々？見せたいものがある？
What is it? Something you want to show me?
あのモニターを見ろって？
Look at that monitor?
3、2、1...
3, 2, 1...
え？どういうこと？お誕生日おめでとう？
Huh? What's going on? "Happy Birthday"?
ええー！ありがとう！
Whaaat?! Thank you!
サプライズしてくれたんだ。
You surprised me.
嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
いつも一番近くで応援してくれて
For always being right by my side to cheer me on,
本当にありがとう。
thank you so very much.
これからもよろしくね。
I'm counting on you from now on, too.
綺麗...
So pretty...
素敵な誕生日にしてくれて、ありがとう。
Thank you for making this such a wonderful birthday.
お礼にこの後、
As a thank you, after this,
君だけのアンコールライブするね。
I'll do an encore live just for you.
これからもずっと一緒にいてね。
Stay with me forever, okay?
今日はお誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！新衣装のAZKiもよろしくね！！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday today! I hope you'll love the new outfit AZKi too!!
今日はお誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday today!
新衣装のAZKiもよろしくね！！
Please look forward to AZKi in her new outfit!!
AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet Pop Story
AZKi 7th Birthday Live: Sweet Pop Story
新衣装お披露目＆重大発表あり
New Outfit Reveal & Major Announcement!